A Guide to the Lois Davidson Gottlieb Architectural Collection, 1945-2003
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Project Records, 1951-2002
  - Drawings, 1951-2002, undated
    - Worden Addition, Riverside, CA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 10)
    - Wright Deck, unknown location, 1977.
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Zigas Remodel, San Francisco, CA, 1986.
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 4)
  - Files, 1951-1996, undated
    This subseries includes notes, invoices, correspondence, sketches, printed and other material resulting from Gottlieb's design activities on various residential projects. Files are arranged chronologically according to project.
    - Connor House, Seattle, WA, 1988. (Box-folder 5-9)
    - De Lada Cabinet, undated (Box-folder 5-14)
    - Daniels Project, Olympia, WA, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 5-5)
    - Erickson Studio, 1976. (Box-folder 4-7)
    - Galante Residence, Carmel, CA, 1986. (Box-folder 5-7)
    - Gottlieb House, 1979. (Box-folder 4-12)
    - Gottlieb House, Olympia, WA, 1981. (Box-folder 5-3)
    - Gulden House, Olympia, WA, 1978. (Box-folder 4-10)
    - Gottlieb House, Riverside, CA, 1964. (Box-folder 4-4)
    - Hansen House, Seattle, WA, 1974, 1978-1979. (Box-folder 4-5)
    - Harrah House, Sedona, AZ, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-2)
    - Haskell Projects, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 5-10)
    - Heidar House, 1979. (Box-folder 4-13)
    - Herring House, undated (Box-folder 5-15)
    - Hobe Project, San Mateo, CA, 1989. (Box-folder 5-11)
    - Humphrey House, Olympia, WA, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 5-4)
    - Low Cost House and Remodeling Project (unfinished), 1996. (Box-folder 5-13)
    - Lynn House, Ketchum, ID, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-1)
    - McLean Bible Church, McLean, VA. (Box-folder 5-18)
    - Maimoni Residence, Orinda, CA, 1985. (Box-folder 5-6)
    - Park Residence, Olympia, WA, 1979. (Box-folder 4-14)
    - Schiff House, undated (Box-folder 5-16)
    - Scriven Project, Riverside, CA, undated (Box-folder 5-17)
    - Sister Emelda Maria, Kitchen and other plans, The College of the Holy Names, Oakland, CA, 1964. (Box-folder 4-3)
    - Val Goeschen House, Inverness, CA, 1951. (Box-folder 4-1,2)
    - Skove Project, Olympia, WA, 1979. (Box-folder 4-15)
    - Stross Project, Orinda, CA, 1974-1978. (Box-folder 4-6)
    - Wheelis Project, Olympia, WA, 1978. (Box-folder 4-11)
    - Wilhelmy Project, Rancho Sante Fe, CA, 1976. (Box-folder 4-8)
    - Worden Project, Riverside, CA, 1977. (Box-folder 4-9)
    - Work for Mark Gottlieb's Company, Design Tech, Fairfax Station, VA, 1996. (Box-folder 5-12)
    - Zigas Project, San Francisco, CA, 1987. (Box-folder 5-8)